I used to think about it as, you could take care of your health, or you could take care of obligations, and one always came at the cost of the other. So now, several hundred of these walking meetings later, I've learned a few things. First, there's this amazing thing about actually getting out of the box that leads to out-of-the-box thinking. Whether it's nature or the exercise itself, it certainly works. And second, and probably the more reflective one, is just about how much each of us can hold problems in opposition when they're really not that way. And if we're going to solve problems and look at the world really differently, whether it's in governance or business or environmental issues, job creation, maybe we can think about how to reframe those problems as having both things be true. Because it was when that happened with this walk-and-talk idea that things became doable and sustainable and viable. So I started this talk talking about the tush, so I'll end with the bottom line, which is, walk and talk. Walk the talk. You'll be surprised at how fresh air drives fresh thinking, and in the way that you do, you'll bring into your life an entirely new set of ideas. Thank you. (Applause)
la forma en que pensaba era que podías cuidar tu salud o cumplir con tus obligaciones, y siempre era uno a costa del otro. Ahora, luego de cientos de estas reuniones a pie, he aprendido algunas cosas. Primero, hay algo increíble al salir realmente de la caja que te lleva a pensar fuera de la caja. Bien sea la naturaleza o el ejercicio mismo, de verdad funciona. Y segundo, probablemente la más reflexiva, es lo mucho que podemos mantener los problemas en oposición cuando en realidad no es así. Y si vamos a resolver problemas y mirar el mundo desde una perspectiva realmente distinta, ya sea en el gobierno o en los negocios, cuestiones ambientales o creación de empleos, quizá podemos pensar cómo replantear esos problemas considerando que ambas partes son posibles. Porque fue cuando eso ocurrió con esta idea de caminar y platicar que las cosas se volvieron realizables, sostenibles y viables. Comencé esta charla hablando acerca del trasero, así que terminaré con la línea final, que es, caminen y platiquen. Pongan el ejemplo. Les sorprenderá ver cómo el aire fresco impulsa el pensamiento innovador, y de esa forma, incorporarán a su vida un conjunto de ideas completamente nuevo. Gracias. (Aplausos)